<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <StatDef>
    <defName>StuffPower_Armor_Blast</defName>
    <label>Armor - Blast</label>
    <labelForFullStatList>Armor - Blast (material factor)</labelForFullStatList>
    <description>Armor against blast damage from explosions.</description>
    <category>StuffStatFactors</category>
    <defaultBaseValue>0</defaultBaseValue>
    <minValue>0</minValue>
    <toStringStyle>PercentZero</toStringStyle>
    <showIfUndefined>false</showIfUndefined>
    <displayPriorityInCategory>4509</displayPriorityInCategory>
  </StatDef>

  <StatDef ParentName="ArmorRatingBase">
    <defName>ArmorRating_Blast</defName>
    <label>Armor - Blast</label>
    <labelForFullStatList>Armor - Blast (armor stat)</labelForFullStatList>
    <description>The protection given against high-pressure shock wave damage caused by explosions, such as blast injuries that can lead to torn organs and other severe conditions.

Upon taking damage, this armor rating is initially reduced by the blast's armor penetration value.

The remaining armor rating is then measured against a random number from 0 to 100.

    - If the random number is under half the armor rating, the shock wave is deflected harmlessly, reducing injury severity.
    - If the random number is over half the armor rating, but not higher than the armor rating, the blast's impact is reduced by half, mitigating risk of severe organ damage.
    - If the random number is greater than the armor rating, the armor provides no protection against the blast's shock wave.

For example, at 90% armor rating against a blast with 10% armor penetration, there is a 40% chance of deflecting the shock wave harmlessly, and a 40% chance of reducing its impact.

Each layer of armor is calculated separately, from the outside in, enhancing overall protection.</description>
    <displayPriorityInCategory>99</displayPriorityInCategory>
    <parts>
      <li Class="StatPart_Stuff">
        <priority>100</priority>
        <stuffPowerStat>StuffPower_Armor_Blast</stuffPowerStat>
        <multiplierStat>StuffEffectMultiplierArmor</multiplierStat>
      </li>
    </parts>
  </StatDef>

</Defs>